[
    {
        "front": "いえ",
        "back": "家 \nhouse",
        "chapter": "N4 K12"
    },
    {
        "front": "かぞく",
        "back": "家族 \nfamily",
        "chapter": "N4 K12"
    },
    {
        "front": "かない",
        "back": "家内 \nwife (for only yours)",
        "chapter": "N4 K12"
    },
    {
        "front": "がか",
        "back": "画家 \npainter",
        "chapter": "N4 K12"
    },
    {
        "front": "かてい",
        "back": "家庭 \nfamily, household",
        "chapter": "N4 K12"
    },
    {
        "front": "かぞく",
        "back": "家族 \nfamily",
        "chapter": "N4 K12"
    },
    {
        "front": "みんぞく",
        "back": "民族 \nrace, mankind",
        "chapter": "N4 K12"
    },
    {
        "front": "すいぞくかん",
        "back": "水族館 \naquarium",
        "chapter": "N4 K12"
    },
    {
        "front": "わたし",
        "back": "私 \nme, i",
        "chapter": "N4 K12"
    },
    {
        "front": "しりつ",
        "back": "私立 \nprivate",
        "chapter": "N4 K12"
    },
    {
        "front": "しせいかつ",
        "back": "私生活 \npersonal life",
        "chapter": "N4 K12"
    },
    {
        "front": "みずから",
        "back": "自ら \noneself",
        "chapter": "N4 K12"
    },
    {
        "front": "じぶん",
        "back": "自分 \noneself",
        "chapter": "N4 K12"
    },
    {
        "front": "じどう",
        "back": "自動 \nautomatic",
        "chapter": "N4 K12"
    },
    {
        "front": "じどうし",
        "back": "自動詞 \nintransitive verbs",
        "chapter": "N4 K12"
    },
    {
        "front": "じゆう",
        "back": "自由 \nfreedom",
        "chapter": "N4 K12"
    },
    {
        "front": "じゆうに",
        "back": "自由に \nfreely",
        "chapter": "N4 K12"
    },
    {
        "front": "しぜん",
        "back": "自然 \nnature",
        "chapter": "N4 K12"
    },
    {
        "front": "しぜんに",
        "back": "自然に \nnaturally",
        "chapter": "N4 K12"
    },
    {
        "front": "おや",
        "back": "親子 \nparents",
        "chapter": "N4 K12"
    },
    {
        "front": "りょうしん",
        "back": "両親 \nparents",
        "chapter": "N4 K12"
    },
    {
        "front": "ははおや",
        "back": "母親 \nmother",
        "chapter": "N4 K12"
    },
    {
        "front": "ちちおや",
        "back": "父親 \nfather",
        "chapter": "N4 K12"
    },
    {
        "front": "しんせつ",
        "back": "親切 \nkind",
        "chapter": "N4 K12"
    },
    {
        "front": "したしい",
        "back": "親しい \nclose ones",
        "chapter": "N4 K12"
    },
    {
        "front": "りょうしん",
        "back": "両親 \nparents",
        "chapter": "N4 K12"
    },
    {
        "front": "りょうがわ",
        "back": "両側 \nboth sides",
        "chapter": "N4 K12"
    },
    {
        "front": "りょうほう",
        "back": "両方 \nboth",
        "chapter": "N4 K12"
    },
    {
        "front": "りょうて",
        "back": "両手 \nboth hands",
        "chapter": "N4 K12"
    },
    {
        "front": "りょうがえ",
        "back": "両替 \nmoney exchange",
        "chapter": "N4 K12"
    },
    {
        "front": "あに",
        "back": "兄 \nelder brother",
        "chapter": "N4 K12"
    },
    {
        "front": "きょうだい",
        "back": "兄弟 \nbrothers and sisters",
        "chapter": "N4 K12"
    },
    {
        "front": "おにいさん",
        "back": "お兄さん \nelder brother (someone else's)",
        "chapter": "N4 K12"
    },
    {
        "front": "おとうと",
        "back": "弟 \nyounger brother",
        "chapter": "N4 K12"
    },
    {
        "front": "きょうだい",
        "back": "兄弟 \nbrothers and sisters",
        "chapter": "N4 K12"
    },
    {
        "front": "あね",
        "back": "姉 \nelder sister",
        "chapter": "N4 K12"
    },
    {
        "front": "しまい",
        "back": "姉妹 \nsisters",
        "chapter": "N4 K12"
    },
    {
        "front": "おねえさん",
        "back": "お姉さん \nolder sister(someone else's)",
        "chapter": "N4 K12"
    },
    {
        "front": "いもうと",
        "back": "妹 \nyounger sister",
        "chapter": "N4 K12"
    },
    {
        "front": "しまい",
        "back": "姉妹 \nsisters",
        "chapter": "N4 K12"
    },
    {
        "front": "しまいとし",
        "back": "姉妹都市 \nsister cities",
        "chapter": "N4 K12"
    }
]